[SPEAKER_00]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, my name is Richard from Monster Reservations Group.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you calling to confirm a reservation today lawyer?
[SPEAKER_00]: I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Give me one second.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me pull up this reservation for you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Are you getting excited to get out of the house for a couple of days?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me see what I got going on here for you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, Ms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Susan and Mr. Chris, I'm sorry, I don't want to mispronounce your last name.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, and that's Endehol, Endehdorf?
[SPEAKER_00]: Eulendorf.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wasn't even close.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, my apologies.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, I got you guys going out here to Cape Canaveral on the 28th of this month, is that correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, this call is recorded for quality as well as training purposes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, I see you set this reservation up on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_00]: So some of what I'm going to run through today might seem a little bit repetitive, but it's going to take me less than three minutes with you, Ms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Susan.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to make sure everything is in order for your reservation, and then I'll be out of your hair like shampoo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_00]: OK.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, I do have you guys checking in at the beautiful Holiday Inn Express and Suites out there on Cocoa Beach.
[SPEAKER_00]: They do, of course, have you guys in that suite unit that doesn't sleep for very comfortably.
[SPEAKER_00]: for the five days and four nights, of course, arriving on Thursday, the 28th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Checking out on the second, that's, of course, going to be that following Monday.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I just have the two adults on this reservation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Does that all sound correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: These next questions I do have for you are very important.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is going to be that repetitive part, like I mentioned.
[SPEAKER_00]: I, of course, have you on this reservation as married, that is legally married, correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys, U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: or Canadian citizens?
[SPEAKER_00]: US.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys, of course, have matching addresses on those driver's license.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those IDs are valid, not expired time of check-in.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_00]: What would you estimate your combined annual income to be prior to taxes a year?
[SPEAKER_00]: Doesn't need to be exact, just an estimate.
[SPEAKER_00]: $500.
[SPEAKER_00]: No bankruptcy, of course, in the last two years, correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: No friends or family traveling on a separate monster package, same date and destination as you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you own any timeshares associated with any vacation clubs?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of you guys can provide a major debit or credit card in your name?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: And are you guys at least 28 years of age or sorry, 25 years of age?
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, Holiday Inn is going to be our premier timeshare developer.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to showcase to you how you can travel to some amazing resorts worldwide.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing they do ask is that you do attend that approximately 120 minute timeshare sales presentation.
[SPEAKER_00]: No obligation to purchase.
[SPEAKER_00]: just to keep that open mind.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can do that for us if we can make it fun and enjoyable for you in return.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course that presentation is scheduled for on the 29th at 11 30 a.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course you will be receiving your $150 back upon completion of that presentation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Besides that the only way that you'll be charged anything additional is if you do not attend that presentation in its entirety.
[SPEAKER_00]: If any of the qualifications I went over don't match up whenever you check in, if you cancel your reservation four days prior to your arrival,
[SPEAKER_00]: or if you guys don't show up whatsoever, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: Have we changed the presentation?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so whenever you guys arrive on property, that'll be the best time to do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's when they have the most open availability.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll go over that time with you as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: Any other questions or concerns I can answer for you today before I let you go?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, we really appreciate you for being the Best 4 About Monster, and you have an absolutely amazing rest of your day, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: You too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye-bye.